Guide to the Henry O'Reilly Papers 1819-1880 (Bulk 1844-1860) MS 464
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Telegraph Enterprise, 1844-1861
  - Subseries II.A: Correspondence, 1844-1860, Letters received arranged alphabetically by correspondent; letters sent arranged chronologically.
    - Letters Received: Morse, Samuel F.B. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: Moss, Charles B. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Moss, Charles B. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: N (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received: Nelson, C. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received: Nurse, S.K. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received: O (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: O'Connor, B. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: Olney, Geo. W. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: O'Reilly, J.J. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: O'Reilly, J.J. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: Oslere, C.G. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: Oslere, Louisa G. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Ottinger, Jos. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: P (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: Packard, Jason B. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: Park, Austin F. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Parmenter, Wm. H. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: Parmenter, Wm. H. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received: Partridge, A.J. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received: Pease, E.H. and Co. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received: Pease, Francis S. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Letters Received: Peck, John A. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received: Peck, Paschal P. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received: Perkins, J.B. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received: Perkins, J.B. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: Phillipe, J.D. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: Pirtle, Henry (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: Pitts, E. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: Q (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: R (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: Ransom, W.B. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Reid, James D. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: Reid, James D. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: Reilly, J.J. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: Richards, W.F. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Ritter, F.W. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: Rodgers, Henry (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received: Rogers, Henry (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received: Roggen, J.J. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received: Ross, John (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Letters Received: Rowe, Stanhope S. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Letters Received: Rutherford, F.S. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Letters Received: Rutherford, J.M. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Letters Received: S-Sm (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received: Sn-Sy (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received: Sanders, J. Milton (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received: Sanford, Wm. E. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: Satterly, Charles (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: Selden, H.R. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: Selden, H.R. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: Sheafe, Chas. H. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: Sherwood, Lorenzo and Luman (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: Sibley, Hiram (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Skinner, Jas. R. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: Smith, Charles T. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: Smith, Francis O.J. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: Smith, J.B. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Smith, S.D. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: Smith, Sanford J. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received: Snyder, W.H. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received: Speed, J.J. Jr. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received: Stager, Anson (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received: Stanton, E.M. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received: Starr, Peter (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received: Steele, Ed. G. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: Stevens, Edwards and Meed (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: Stitt, John (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: Stockton, J.A. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: Sturdivant and White (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: Sutliff, E.A. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: Swaim, Jas (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Swaim, W.M. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: T (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: Terry, W.D. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: Thayer, Wm. S. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Thomas, B.M. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: Tibbits, H.B. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received: Tifft, S. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received: Townsend, R. and Co. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received: Treat, Samuel (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Letters Received: Trowbridge, Wm. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Letters Received: U (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Letters Received: Urquhart, M.H. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Letters Received: V (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Letters Received: Veitch, Isaac M. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Letters Received: Voris, Francis (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Letters Received: W-Wh (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Letters Received: Wi-Wr (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Letters Received: Wade, J.H. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Letters Received: Ward, James W. (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Letters Received: Ward, James W. (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Letters Received: Ware, Henry (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received: Washburn, I. and Co. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received: Wheeler, A.J. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received: White, Geo. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: Wildes, D.S. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: Wilson, C.S. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: Wilson, R.A. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: Witman, Eugene L. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: Woolfolk, Rich. H. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: Woolfolk, Rich. H. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Worthington and Pullan (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: Worthington, L. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: Wright, E. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: Y (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Zook, S.K. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: Zook, S.K. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1851 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1852 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1854 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1857 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1858 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1859 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received, Unidentified, 1860 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received, Multiple Telegraph Messages, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received, Multiple Telegraph Messages, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received, Multiple Telegraph Messages, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received, Multiple Telegraph Messages, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Letters Received, Multiple Telegraph Messages, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Letters Received, Multiple Telegraph Messages, 1851 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Letters Sent: Fragments (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1844 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1845 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1846 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1847 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1847 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1848 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1848 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1849 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1849 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1849 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1849 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1851 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1851 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1851 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1852 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1852 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1852 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1853 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1853 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1854 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1856 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1857 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1857 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1858 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1858 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1858 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1859 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1860 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1861 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Letters Between Others, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Letters Between Others, 1846 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Letters Between Others, 1847 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Letters Between Others, 1848 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Letters Between Others, 1848 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Letters Between Others, 1849 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Letters Between Others, 1849 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Letters Between Others, 1850 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Letters Between Others, 1850 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Letters Between Others, 1850 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Letters Between Others, 1851 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Letters Between Others, 1852 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Letters Between Others, 1852 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Letters Between Others, 1853 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Letters Between Others, 1853 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Letters Between Others, 1854 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Letters Between Others, 1855 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Letters Between Others, 1856 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Letters Between Others, 1857 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Letters Between Others, 1858 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Letters Between Others, 1859 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Subseries II.B: Organizational Documents, 1845-1859, Arranged chronologically.
    - Organizational Documents, Undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Organizational Documents, 1845 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Organizational Documents, 1846 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Organizational Documents, 1847 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Organizational Documents, 1848 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Organizational Documents, 1849 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Organizational Documents, 1850 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Organizational Documents, 1857 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Organizational Documents, 1858 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Organizational Documents, 1859 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Subseries II.C: Legal Documents, 1837-1846, Arranged chronologically.
    - Legal Documents, Undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Legal Documents, Undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Legal Documents, Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Legal Documents, Undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Legal Documents, 1837 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Legal Documents, 1838 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Legal Documents, 1843 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Legal Documents, 1845 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Legal Documents, 1846 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Legal Documents, 1847 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Legal Documents, 1847 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Legal Documents, 1848 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Legal Documents, 1848 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, 1849 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Legal Documents, 1849 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Legal Documents, 1850 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Legal Documents, 1850 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Legal Documents, 1851 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Legal Documents, 1851 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Legal Documents, 1852 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Legal Documents, 1853 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, 1854 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Legal Documents, 1855 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Legal Documents, 1856 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Legal Documents, 1857 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Legal Documents, 1858 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Legal Documents, 1859 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Legal Documents, 1860 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Subseries II.D: Financial Documents, 1844-1859, Arranged chronologically.
    - Financial Documents: General, Undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Financial Documents: General, Undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1844-1846 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1847 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1848 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1848 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1849 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1849 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1850 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1850 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1850 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1851 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1852 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1853 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1854 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1855 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1856 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1857 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1858 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1859 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Financial Documents: Concerning Marshall Lefferts, 1848 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Financial Documents: Concerning Marshall Lefferts, 1849 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Financial Documents: Concerning Marshall Lefferts, 1850 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Financial Documents: Concerning Marshall Lefferts, 1851 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Subseries II.E: Minutes, Proceedings, 1847-1853
    - Minutes, Proceedings, 1847-1853 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Subseries II.F: Notes, 1850
    - Notes, 1850 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Notes, 1850 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Subseries II.G: Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Subseries II.H: Printed Material, 1845-1861
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Printed Material, 1845-1861 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Series III: Demoine Navigation and Railroad Company, 1849-1858, This series documents O'Reilly's activities as secretary of this company, which was organized in 1854 to improve the Demoine Valley.
  - Subseries III.A: Correspondence, 1853-1858, Letters received arranged alphabetically by correspondent; letters sent arranged chronologically.
    - Letters Received: Unidentified (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received: B (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received: Biggs, Uriah (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Letters Received: Blackwell, E.R. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: Bonney, Josiah H. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: Browne, J. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: C (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: Clark, Orville (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: Cuming, T.B. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: D (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Dodge, A.C. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: E (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: F (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: G (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: Gaylord, G. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: Gillaspy, Geo. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received: Grimes, James W. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received: H (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received: Henn, Bernhart (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Letters Received: Hunt, A. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Letters Received: Hunt, W. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Letters Received: I (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Letters Received: J (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Letters Received: Johnson, Reverdy (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Letters Received: Johnson, W.C. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Letters Received: K (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Letters Received: L (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Letters Received: M (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Letters Received: Mann, Donald (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Letters Received: N (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Letters Received: P (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Letters Received: R (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Letters Received: S (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Letters Received: Seely, Sam J. (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Letters Received: Speed, J.J., Jr. (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Letters Received: T (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Letters Received: V (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Letters Received: W (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Letters Received: Wright, George C. (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Letters Received: Y (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Letters Received: Z (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Letters Sent, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1853 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1854 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1854 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1854 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1854 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1854 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1855 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1856 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1856 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1857 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1858 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Letters Between Others, 1854-1857 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.B: Organizational Documents, 1850-1855, Arranged chronologically.
    - Organizational Documents, 1850-1855 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III.C: Proceedings, 1851-1856, Arranged chronologically.
    - Proceedings, Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings, 1851 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings, 1854 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings, 1855 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings, 1855 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings, 1856 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III.D: Legal Documents, 1849-1854, Arranged chronologically.
    - Legal Documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Legal Documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Legal Documents, 1849 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Legal Documents, 1852 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Legal Documents, 1853 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Legal Documents, 1854 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Legal Documents, 1854 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Legal Documents, 1855 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Legal Documents, 1856 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Legal Documents, 1857 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, 1858 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III.E: Financial Documents, 1845-1857, Arranged chronologically.
    - Financial Documents, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Financial Documents, 1845 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Financial Documents, 1847 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Financial Documents, 1853 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Financial Documents, 1854 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Financial Documents, 1855 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Financial Documents, 1856 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Financial Documents, 1857 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Subseries III.F: Notes, 1847-1857, Arranged chronologically.
    - Notes, Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Notes, 1846 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Notes, 1849 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Notes, 1854 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Notes, 1855-1857 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Subseries III.G: Miscellaneous, 1854
    - Miscellaneous, 1854 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Subseries III.H: Printed Material, 1854-1858
    - Printed Material (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Printed Material (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Printed Material (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Series IV: Erie Canal Enlargement, 1836-1841, Series IV briefly documents O'Reilly's interest in rebuilding and enlarging the Erie Canal.
  - Subseries IV.A: Correspondence, 1838-1840
    - Letters Received, 1838-1840 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1838-1839 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Subseries IV.B: Notes, 1836-1841
    - Notes, 1836-1841 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Series V: Clinton League, 1859, This series contains documentation on the Clinton League, which was formed in 1859 to protect the New York State canal system from the opposing policies of the state railroad system. This material reflects O'Reilly's activities as chairman of the League.
  - Subseries V.A: Correspondence, 1859, Letters received arranged alphabetically by correspondent; letters sent arranged chronologically.
    - Letters Received: Unidentified, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Letters Received: A, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Letters Received: B, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Letters Received: Baker and Godwin, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Letters Received: Barton, J.L., 1859 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Letters Received: Bascom, Ansel, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Letters Received: C, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Letters Received: Cobb, C., 1859 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Letters Received: D, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Letters Received: E, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Letters Received: F, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Letters Received: G, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Letters Received: H, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Letters Received: J, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Letters Received: K, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Letters Received: L, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Letters Received: M, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Letters Received: Mann, Donald, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Letters Received: N, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Letters Received: P, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Letters Received: R, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Letters Received: S, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Letters Received: T, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Letters Received: Tucker, Midmer J., 1859 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Letters Received: V, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Letters Received: W, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Letters Received: Y, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Letters Sent, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Subseries V.B: Minutes, 1859
    - Minutes, 1859 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Subseries V.C: Notes, Undated
    - Notes, Undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Subseries V.D: Printed Material
    - Printed Material (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Printed Material (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Series VI: New York State Agricultural Society, 1841-1856, Series VI is comprised of documents pertaining to various activities of the New York State Agricultural Society, of which O'Reilly was recording secretary. It includes material on the New York State Agricultural Fair of 1844.
  - Subseries VI.A: Correspondence, 1841-1847
    - Letters Received, 1841 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Letters Received, 1844 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Letters Received, 1845 (Box 40, Folder 3)